Lowell Thomas Papers: Periodicals
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 6. Asia, 1920-1938; 1 box
  - Asia Volume XX, Number 8, September 1920 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XX, Number 9, October 1920 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XX, Number 9, October 1920 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XX, Number 10, November 1920 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XX, Number 11, December 1920 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXI, Number 1, January 1921 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXI, Number 2, February 1921 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXI, Number 3, March 1921 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXI, Number 4, April 1921 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXI, Number 5, May 1921 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXI, Number 5, May 1921 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXI, Number 6, June 1921 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXII, Number 4, April 1922 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXII, Number 5, May 1922 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIV, Number 1, January 1924 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIV, Number 4, April 1924 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIV, Number 5, May 1924 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIV, Number 10, October 1924 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIV, Number 12, December 1924 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXV, Number 2, February 1925 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXV, Number 10, October 1925 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXV, Number 11, November 1925 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXV, Number 12, December 1925 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVI, Number 10, October 1926 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVI, Number 12, December 1926 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 1, January 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 2, February 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 3, March 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 4, April 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 5, May 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 6, June 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 7, July 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 8, August 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 9, September 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 10, October 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVII, Number 11, November 1927 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVIII, Number 1, January 1928 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVIII, Number 2, February 1928 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVIII. Number 3, March 1928 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVIII, Number 4, April 1928 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVIII, Number 4, April 1928 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXVIII, Number 6, June 1928 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIX, Number 4, April 1929 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIX, Number 6, June 1929 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIX, Number 7, July 1929 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIX, Number 10, October 1929 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIX, Number 11, November 1929 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXIX, Number 12, December 1929 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXX, Number 2, February 1930 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXX, Number 4, April 1930 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXX, Number 7, July 1930 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXX, Number 8, August 1930 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXX, Number 11, November 1930 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXX, Number 12, December 1930 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXXI, Number 1, January 1931 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXXI, Number 2, February 1931 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXXI, Number 4, April 1931 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXXI, Number 3, May 1931 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXXIV, Number 3, March 1934 (Box 19)
  - Asia Volume XXXVIII, Number 4, April 1938 (Box 19)
- 7. Blackwood's Magazine, 1952-1957
  Series contains issues from Blackwood’s Magazine.
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1642 Volume 272, August 1952 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1646 Volume 272, December 1952 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1647 Volume 273, January 1953 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1648 Volume 273, February 1953 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1649 Volume 273, March 1953 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1650 Volume 273, April 1953 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1651 Volume 273, May 1953 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1652 Volume 273, June 1953 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1653 Volume 274, July 1953 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1660 Volume 275, February 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1661 Volume 275, March 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1662 Volume 275, April 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1663 Volume 275, May 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1665 Volume 276, July 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1666 Volume 276, August 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1667 Volume 276, September 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1668 Volume 276, October 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1669 Volume 276, November 1954 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1673 Volume 277, March 1955 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1675 Volume 277, May 1955 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1677 Volume 278, July 1955 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1681 Volume 278, November 1955 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1682 Volume 278, December 1955 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1685 Volume 279, March 1956 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1698 Volume 281, April 1957 (Box 20)
  - Blackwood's Magazine Number 1705 Volume 282, November 1957 (Box 20)
- 8. Reader's Digest, 1936-1982; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Reader’s Digest.
  - Reader's Digest, March 1936 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, December 1948 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, April 1961 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, April 1961 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, April 1961 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, August 1961 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, December 1962 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, June 1970 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, February 1972 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, June 1972 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, December 1974 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, January 1975 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, June 1975 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, February 1977 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, July 1977 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, September 1977 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, October 1977 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, October 1977 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, December 1977 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, April 1978 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, May 1978 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, August 1978 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, October 1978 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, December 1978 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, February 1979 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, September 1979 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, October 1979 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, December 1979 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, June 1980 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, August 1980 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, October 1980 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, January 1981 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, February 1981 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, March 1981 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, January 1982 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, March 1982 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, April 1982 (Box 20)
  - Reader's Digest, September 1982 (Box 20)
- 9. Television Daily, 1959; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Television Daily.
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 47, March 12, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 48, March 13, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 49, March 16, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 50, March 17, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 51, March 18, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 52, March 19, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 53, March 20, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 54, March 23, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 55, March 24, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 56, March 25, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 57, March 26, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 58, March 27, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85, NO. 59, March 30, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 85 NO. 60, March 31, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 86, NO. 1, April 1, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 86, NO. 1, April 1, 1959 (Box 21)
  - Television Daily VOL. 86, NO. 4, April 6, 1959 (Box 21)
- 10. Canadian Geographical Journal, 1946-1983; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Canadian Geographical Journal.
  - Canadian Geographical Journal Vol. XXXII No. 5, May 1946 (Box 21)
  - Canadian Geographical Journal Vol. LXI No. 6, December 1960 (Box 21)
  - Canadian Geographical Journal Vol. LXII No. 5, May 1961 (Box 21)
  - Canadian Geographical Journal Volume LXX No. 4, April 1965 (Box 21)
  - Canadian Geographical Journal Volume LXXI No. 3, September 1965 (Box 21)
  - Canadian Geographical Journal Volume LXXI No. 4, October 1965 (Box 21)
  - Canadian Geographical Journal Volume LXXX No. 3, March 1970 (Box 21)
  - Canadian Geographic Volume 100, Number 3, June-July 1980 (Box 21)
  - Canadian Geographic Volume 103, Number 4, August-September 1983 (Box 21)
- 11. American Heritage, 1979-1981; 1 box
  Series contains issues of American Heritage.
  - American Heritage Volume 30/Number 6, October-November 1979 (Box 21)
  - American Heritage Volume 31/Number 4, June-July 1980 (Box 21)
  - American Heritage Volume 31/Number 5, August-September 1980 (Box 21)
  - American Heritage Volume 31/Number 6, October-November 1980 (Box 21)
  - American Heritage Volume 32/Number 2, February-March 1981 (Box 21)
- 12. Natural History, 1940-1973; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Natural History.
  - Natural History Volume XLVI. No. 5, December 1940 (Box 21)
  - Natural History Volume XLVI. No. 5, December 1940 (Box 21)
  - Natural History VOL. LXXIX, No. 3, March 1970 (Box 21)
  - Natural History VOL. LXXIX, No. 6, June-July 1970 (Box 21)
  - Natural History VOL. LXXIX, No. 8, October 1970 (Box 21)
  - Natural History VOL. LXXXII, No. 10, December 1973 (Box 21)
- 13. The New Yorker, 1951-1981; 1 box
  Series contains issues of The New Yorker.
  - The New Yorker, August 4, 1951 (Box 21)
  - The New Yorker, June 14, 1958 (Box 21)
  - The New Yorker, April 4, 1970 (Box 21)
  - The New Yorker, June 1, 1981 (Box 21)
- 14. Collier's, 1941-1951; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Collier’s.
  - Collier's VOL. 63, NO. 20, May 17, 1919 (Box 21)
  - Collier's, May 10, 1941 (Box 21)
  - Collier's, August 26, 1944 (Box 21)
  - Collier's, February 9, 1946 (Box 21)
  - Collier's, October 20, 1951 (Box 21)
- 15. The Rinter, 1942-1944; 1 box
  Series contains issues of The Rinter.
  - The Rinter Volume XX Number 1, September 11, 1942 (Box 21)
  - The Rinter Volume XX, No. 9, January 2, 1943 (Box 21)
  - The Rinter Volume XX Number 19, May 21, 1943 (Box 21)
  - The Rinter Volume XXI Number 12, February 18, 1944 (Box 21)
- 16. Sports Illustrated, 1966-1974; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Sports Illustrated.
  - Sports Illustrated, March 21, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Sports Illustrated, August 8, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Sports Illustrated, October 19, 1970 (Box 21)
  - Sports Illustrated, July 8, 1974 (Box 21)
- 17. Rockefeller Center Weekly, 1934-1936; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Rockefeller Center Weekly.
  - Rockefeller Center Weekly VOL. 1, NO. 11, December 13, 1934 (Box 21)
  - Rockefeller Center Weekly VOL. 3, NO. 12, September 26, 1935 (Box 21)
  - Rockefeller Center Weekly VOL. 3, NO. 13, October 3, 1935 (Box 21)
  - Rockefeller Center Weekly VOL. 3, NO. 14, October 10, 1935 (Box 21)
  - Rockefeller Center Weekly VOL. 5, NO. 8, August 21, 1936 (Box 21)
- 18. Saks News, 1948-1949; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Saks News.
  - Saks News Vol. 3 No. 10, February 1948 (Box 21)
  - Saks News Vol. 3 No. 11, March 1948 (Box 21)
  - Saks News Vol. 4 No. 4, November 1948 (Box 21)
  - Saks News Vol. 4 No. 10, Fall 1949 (Box 21)
- 19. Life, 1953-1963; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Life.
  - Life, August 9, 1943 (Box 21)
  - Life, December 28, 1953 (Box 21)
  - Life John F. Kennedy Memorial Edition, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Life, August 11, 1967 (Box 21)
- 20. Liberty, 1935-1936; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Liberty.
  - Liberty VOL. 9, NO. 45, November 5, 1932 (Box 21)
  - Liberty VOL. 12, NO. 38, September 21, 1935 (Box 21)
  - Liberty VOL. 13, NO. 40, October 3, 1936 (Box 21)
  - Liberty VOL. 16, NO. 17, April 29, 1939 (Box 21)
- 21. Book Digest Magazine, 1976-1980; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Book Digest Magazine.
  - Book Digest Magazine, May 1976 (Box 21)
  - Book Digest Magazine, August 1976 (Box 21)
  - Book Digest Magazine, May 1977 (Box 21)
  - Book Digest Magazine, May 1978 (Box 21)
  - Book Digest Magazine, November 1980 (Box 21)
- 22. Miscellany, 1920-1981; 2 boxes
  Series contains issues of various periodicals.
  - Magna Charta, February 23, 1920 (Box 22)
  - Peoples of All Nations, Circa 1920 (Box 22)
  - Peoples of All Nations, October 10, 1922 (Box 22)
  - Peoples of All Nations, Circa 1922 (Box 22)
  - Peoples of All Nations, February 13, 1923 (Box 22)
  - The Mentor, May 1924 (Box 22)
  - The American Magazine Vol. XCVIII, No. 3, September 1924 (Box 22)
  - The American Magazine Vol. XCVIII, No. 4, October 1924 (Box 22)
  - World's Work Vol. LIII. No. 3, January 1927 (Box 22)
  - Airways Magazine Vol. III. No. 6, February 1927 (Box 22)
  - Aviation The Oldest American Aeronautical Magazine VOLUME XXII NUMBER 11, March 14, 1927 (Box 22)
  - The World's Work Vol. LVI. No. 6, October 1928 (Box 22)
  - The World's Work Vol. LVII. No. 1, November 1928 (Box 22)
  - World's Work, May 1929 (Box 22)
  - Nature Magazine VOL. 19, NO. 5, May 1932 (Box 22)
  - International Detective Magazine, November 1933 (Box 22)
  - The February 1935 Sun Dial Magazine of the Sun Oil Co. (Box 22)
  - St. Nicholas, May 1935 (Box 22)
  - Farm Journal, December 1935 (Box 22)
  - Bergama Kermesi, 1937 (Box 22)
  - Journal of Living Eat to Stay Young with the Years, 1937 (Box 22)
  - The Quill, January 1938 (Box 22)
  - Consumers' Research Bulletin Vol. 4, No. 8, April 1938 (Box 22)
  - Bergama Kermesi, May 22-28, 1938 (Box 22)
  - Time Volume XXXIII Number 13, March 27, 1939 (Box 22)
  - Town & Country, April 1939 (Box 22)
  - Farm Journal and Farmer's Wife, July 1939 (Box 22)
  - Junior League Magazine, December 1939 (Box 22)
  - The Elks Magazine, November 1940 (Box 22)
  - New Horizons The Magazine of America's Merchant Marine of the Air, November 1941 (Box 22)
  - Ski Illustrated, Christmas 1941 (Box 22)
  - The Gallery of Stars, 1941 (Box 22)
  - Think Vol. IX No. 6, June 1943 (Box 22)
  - Smithsonian Institution War Background Studies Number Thirteen, July 8, 1943 (Box 22)
  - Coronet, August 1945 (Box 22)
  - Time Volume XLVI Number 11, September 10, 1945 (Box 22)
  - The Quill A Magazine for Writers, Editors, and Publishers, September-October 1945 (Box 22)
  - Ilkokul Cografya Atlasi, 1945 (Box 22)
  - Sky and Telescope Vol. V, No. 8 Whole Number 56, June 1946 (Box 22)
  - Mevlananin Turbesi, October 6, 1946 (Box 22)
  - The American Magazine, October 1948 (Box 22)
  - This Week Magazine Section 8, November 20, 1949 (Box 22)
  - The American Mercury Vol. LXXII, No. 327, March 1951 (Box 22)
  - The Saturday Evening Post, June 9, 1951 (Box 22)
  - Fortune, February 1952 (Box 22)
  - Consumers' Research Bulletin, June 1952 (Box 22)
  - Modern Industry The monthly magazine for executives in industry, June 15, 1952 (Box 22)
  - Camel Brands and Graffiti from Iraq, Syria, Jordan, Iran, and Arabia Number 15, October-December 1952 (Box 22)
  - N.A.S. [Naval Air Station] Annual, January 1953 (Box 22)
  - The Mayflower Promenade Magazine, November 1953 (Box 22)
  - The Hollywood Reporter Vol. CXXXIV, No. 2, March 31, 1955 (Box 22)
  - The Hollywood Reporter Vol. CXXXIV, No. 3, April 1, 1955 (Box 23)
  - Daily Variety Vol. 87 No. 20, April 1, 1955 (Box 23)
  - Maritime Industrial Empire The Story of Dosco, January 1957 (Box 23)
  - Women Lawyers Journal VOL. XLIII No. 4, Fall 1957 (Box 23)
  - The Mediterranean and Eurafrica Vol. I, No. 1, June 1958 (Box 23)
  - U.S. News & World Report, July 11, 1958 (Box 23)
  - Arab World, March 1959 (Box 23)
  - Gold in Australia National Gold Magazine VOL. 32. No. 11, August 1959 (Box 23)
  - TV Prevue Vol. 5, No. 8, [1959] (Box 23)
  - Ski, February 1960 (Box 23)
  - This Week Magazine, November 13, 1960 (Box 23)
  - Australian Territories Vol. 1, No. 4, June 1961 (Box 23)
  - Atlas The Magazine of the World Press VOL. 2, NO. 5, November 1961 (Box 23)
  - Australian Territories Vol. 2, No. 1, January 1962 (Box 23)
  - Town & Country, January 1963 (Box 23)
  - Australian Territories Vol. 3, No. 2, March 1963 (Box 23)
  - Holiday: An Entire Issue On Russia VOL. 34, NO. 4, October 1963 (Box 23)
  - Sets in Order The Official Magazine of Square Dancing, November 1963 (Box 23)
  - Esquire Magazine, December 1963 (Box 23)
  - The Arab World Special Issue, [1965] (Box 23)
  - United States Naval Institute Proceedings Reprint No. 757, Vol. 92, No. 3, March 1966 (Box 23)
  - The Classical Bulletin Volume 42, Number 5, March 1966 (Box 23)
  - Soviet Life, September 1966 (Box 23)
  - Focus VOL. XVII, NO. 5, January 1967 (Box 23)
  - Focus VOL. XVII, NO. 6, February 1967 (Box 23)
  - Holiday VOL. 42, NO. 1, July 1967 (Box 23)
  - The Polar Times No. 65, December 1967 (Box 23)
  - House Beautiful Scandinavia, January 1968 (Box 23)
  - Fortune VOL. LXXVII NO. 5, May 1968 (Box 23)
  - The Daily Telegraph Magazine Number 210, October 11, 1968 (Box 23)
  - The Daily Telegraph Magazine Number 210, October 11, 1968 (Box 23)
  - Ohioana Quarterly Volume XII Number 1, Spring 1969 (Box 23)
  - The Polar Times No. 69, December 1969 (Box 23)
  - Bits & Pieces A Monthly Mixture of Horse Sense and Common Sense About Working with People Volume B Number 3, 1969 (Box 23)
  - 20th Century Reflections The 1969 Alumni College Lectures - III The Rise and Fall of Humanity (Box 23)
  - 20th Century Reflections The 1969 Alumni College Lectures - IV The Dilemma of World Power (Box 23)
  - Signature, February 1970 (Box 23)
  - National Parks Magazine, February 1970 (Box 23)
  - National Parks Magazine, March 1970 (Box 23)
  - Travel: The Magazine that Roams the Globe, August 1970 (Box 23)
  - Forbes, October 1, 1970 (Box 23)
  - Venture The Traveler's World, May 1971 (Box 23)
  - Travel & Leisure, June-July 1971 (Box 23)
  - The Voyages of RA, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Arctic VOLUME 26, NUMBER 2, June 1973 (Box 23)
  - Chicago History, Spring-Summer 1974 (Box 23)
  - FBI Law Enforcement Bulletin, August 1974 (Box 23)
  - Animal Kingdom, August-September 1976 (Box 23)
  - Portfolio The Magazine of the Visual Arts Vol. I, No. 1, April-May 1979 (Box 23)
  - Portfolio The Magazine of the Visual Arts Vol. I, No. 2, June-July 1979 (Box 23)
  - Portfolio The Magazine of the Visual Arts Vol. I, No. 4, October-November 1979 (Box 23)
  - TWA Ambassador, June 1980 (Box 23)
  - Ladies' Home Journal, July 1980 (Box 23)
  - Smithsonian, November 1980 (Box 23)
  - Travel The Magazine that Roams the Globe, March 1981 (Box 23)
  - The Magazine Antiques, April 1981 (Box 23)
  - Chronicles of Culture Volume 5, Number 3, May-June 1981 (Box 23)
  - New York, June 1, 1981 (Box 23)
  - The Magazine Antiques, July 1981 (Box 23)
  - The Quill A Magazine for Writers, Editors, and Publishers, December 1981 (Box 23)
  - Dateline Overseas Press Club of America 1981 (Box 23)